deterred
deter /dɪˈtɜ:/vt. 阻止;制止;威慑;使不敢;阻碍;Don’t let failure deter you.别让失败把你吓倒。

spectacular
spectacular /spekˈtækjulə/adj. 壮观的, 雄伟的, 引人入胜的;惊人的;n. 壮观的场面;精彩的表演;This is a spectacular film.这是一部场面壮观的电影。

banged
bang /bæŋ/n. 猛击, 猛撞;巨响, 爆炸声;vt. 猛击, 猛撞;vi. 发出砰的一声, 砰砰作响, 砰地敲[推, 扔];男性和(女性)性交;adv. 正好;完全地;She fell and got a nasty bang on the knee.她摔倒了, 膝盖猛撞在地上。The door shut with a bang.门砰的一声关上了。Bangn. [人名] 班;

wimpy
wimpyadj. 〈俚〉懦弱的,无用的,哭哭啼啼的;

awe
awe /ɔ:/n. 敬畏, 惊惧, 惊叹;vt. 使敬畏, 使惊惧, 使惊叹;The sight filled us with awe.这景色使我们大为惊叹。I was awed by the huge gorilla.那只大猩猩使我惊惧。Awen. [地名] [尼日利亚] 阿韦;AWEabbr. advanced warfighting experiment 先期作战实验;all-weather electronics 全天候电子设备;Alowe, Gabon 加蓬,阿鲁乌机场(代码);asymptotic waveform evaluation method 渐近波形评估法;

detriment
detriment /ˈdetrəmənt/n. 损害, 伤害;造成损害的事物;He sits up very late, to the detriment of his health.他经常熬夜, 损害健康。Smoking is a detriment to one’s health.吸烟危害健康。

ddling
DDLE【医】[=disseminated discod lupus erythematosus]播散性盘状红斑狼疮;

coddling
coddle /ˈkɔdl/vt. 悉心照料, 娇惯;

stance
stance /stæns/n. (运动员的)始发姿势;站姿;被放置的姿势;看法,立场,观点;The boxer took up a fighting stance.拳击手采取了攻势。He has changed his stance on monetary union.他已经改变了对货币联盟的态度。

lineman
lineman /ˈlainmən/n. 养路工人,巡道员;

youth
youth /ju:θ/n. 青年时期, 青春(期)(尤指成年以前);青春, 活力, 朝气, 血气;青年人,,年轻人;年轻人, 青年男子;They studied together in their youth.青少年时期他们就在一起学习。She kept her youth.她青春依旧。The youth of our country have[has] lofty ideals.我国的青年有崇高的理想。The youth of today has greater opportunities than ever before.现在的年轻人比以往任何时候都有更多的机会。

livid
livid /ˈlɪvɪd/adj. <口>大怒的;乌青色的;livid with anger发怒a livid colour铅色

eez
EEZabbr. exclusive economic zone (一国沿海的)专属经济区;

Jeez
jeez /dʒi:z/interj. 呀;

conditioniJ


conditioning
conditioning /kənˈdiʃəniŋ/n. 条件作用;训练;健身训练;condition /kənˈdiʃn/n. 状况, 状态; 地位;健康状况, 可使用的状况;条件, 先决条件;环境, 情况;疾病;(影响某事发生的)物质环境,状态,条件;条件;条款;要件;前提;(某群体的)生存状态,处境;特殊情况,特定环境;地位,身份;【法律】(契约、遗嘱中的)条款,条件;规定;vt. 制约, 限制;使习惯于, 使适应;作为…的条件;规定;决定;约束;置于适当情况,使处于正常状态;【心理学】引起条件反射,使形成条件反射;vt. & vi. 对…具有重要影响;影响(某事发生的方式);保持(头发或皮肤等的)健康;养护;Ability and effort condition success.才干和努力是成功的条件。My expenditure is conditioned by my income.我的支出取决于我的收入。You need to condition yourself if you are to play in the football match on Saturday.如果你要参加星期六的足球比赛,就需要把你自己调整到最佳状态。

hydration
hydrationn. 水合,水合作用;

commissioner
commissioner /kəˈmɪʃənə/n. 专员, 长官;委员;政府部门的长官,警察局长,(美国体育协会的)总干事,主管人;The commissioner has issued a warrant for her arrest.专员发出了对她的逮捕令。The Commissioners of Inland Revenue control British national taxes.国家税收委员管理英国全国的税收。

rant
rant /rænt/vt. & vi. 夸夸其谈,大叫大嚷地以…说教;气愤地)大叫大嚷;不停地大声抱怨;Drink in hand,he ranted about his adventures in Africa.他端着酒杯,激动地叙述他在非洲的经历。He stood there for about twenty minutes ranting and raving about the colour of the new paint.他在那儿站了二十来分钟,大声抱怨新涂料的颜色不够好。Rantn. [人名] 兰特;RANTabbr. Reentry Antenna Test(ing) 反复触动测试;

humiliated
humiliatedadj. 感到羞愧的;humiliate /hjuˈmilieit/vt. 羞辱;使丧失尊严;Parents are humiliated if their children behave badly when guests are present.子女在客人面前举止失当, 父母也失体面。

for
for /fɔ:, fə/prep. (表示时间)在(某一特定时间); 在…时节; 持续达;(表示方向)向, 朝, 开往;(表示对象) 替, 帮, 给, 为…做准备, 对, 对于, 对…来说, 在…一方;(表示原因)因为, 由于, 作为…的结果;(表示距离)延续达, 计有;(表示结果)当做, 作为, 作为…的部分, 就…的条件而言;(表示目的)为了…, 适用于;(表示态度)支持, 赞同, 想要;(表示比率)按…比例, 以…价格, 第…次;(表示对象、用途等)给,对,供;关于;代表;受雇于;支持;拥护;为得到;为获取;换取; 就…而言; 对(某人)来说(困难、必需、愉快等);conj. 因为, 由于;They made a rush for the exit.他们猛然冲向出口处。What can I do for you?我能帮你什么忙吗?I'm pretty angry with you for not telling me.由于你没有告诉我, 我对你很生气。I followed him for some distance.我跟着他走了一段路程。We can't accept that as a basis for a decision.我们不能同意以此为基础来做出决定。The ship sent out a message for help.船只发出求救信号。Are you for the plan or against it?你支持这计划还是反对它呢?I bought this book for ￡3.我买这本书花了三英镑。Prepare to alight, for we are almost there.我们马上要到了, 准备下车吧。FORabbr. Free on Rail 铁路[火车上]交货(价格);Forabbr. force 力;部队,兵力;forint 福林(匈牙利货币单位);Formosa 台湾;formyl 甲酰;Fornax 天炉(星)座;FoRabbr. frequency of relapse 复发性频率;

desperate
desperate /ˈdespərit/adj. 不顾一切的, 拼命的;铤而走险的, 孤注一掷的;极想望的, 极需要的;危急的, 极严重的;He is a desperate criminal.他是个亡命之徒。They made a desperate attempt to save the company.他们为挽救公司作孤注一掷的努力。He's desperate for money.他极渴望得到钱。The city is suffering a desperate shortage of water.这个城市严重缺水。

intricacies
intricacy /ˈɪntrɪkəsi:/n. 错综复杂;(因复杂而产生的)难以理解;(常复数)错综复杂的事物;In software engineering, the degree of complication of a system or system component, determined by such factors as the number and intricacy of interfaces, the number and intricacy of conditional branches, the degree of nesting, the types of data structures, and other system characteristics.在软件工程中,系统或系统组成部分的复杂程度由下述因素确定:接口的数量和错综程度、条件转移的数量和错综程度、嵌套的深度、数据结构的类型,以及其它一些系统特性。

adversity
adversity /ædˈvɜ:sɪti:/n. 逆境;厄运;(经济方面的)窘境;(常作-ties)灾祸;灾难;不幸;Adversity comes with instruction in its hand.逆境给人以教益。Sweet are the uses of adversity.因祸得福。

head
head /hed/n. 头部;领导, 首脑;上端, 顶部, 前端;个人;(牛、羊等)头数;头脑, 智力;头脑;脑筋;(人或动物的)一头长,一头高;(持续的)头痛;硬币正面(有人头像);较宽大的一端;头;(河流)源头;上座(桌子旁最重要的座位);领头位置;排头;(茎梗顶端的)叶球,头状花序;校长;院长;啤酒泡沫;酒头;磁头;蒸汽压力;厕所;vt. 带领; 居…之首; 主管;位于排行之首;排在前头;在(页或篇章的)顶端加标题;用头顶(球);对着…行进,拦挡,拦阻;使朝…方向行进;使走向;使趋向;vi. 朝…行进; 长出头;向…方向移动,朝特定方向前进;[美国英语]发源,起源;adj. 头的;头部的;头上戴的;在前头的;在顶端的;自前面来的;对面的;首长的,领袖的;首要的,首位的;首席的;Write your address at the head of this page.把你的住址写在纸的上端。He has twenty head of cattle on the farm.他在农场养了20头牛。His name heads the list.他的名字居名单之首。The police headed an overspeed car.警察拦住了一辆超速行驶的汽车。Our boat was headed for shore.我们的船朝岸边驶去。You are heading north.你们在往北行进。He heads toward me directly.他径直朝我走来。All experience heads from practice.一切经验源于实践。HEADabbr. High-Explosive Delayed Action 高爆延进炮弹;Headn. [英格兰人姓氏] 黑德。绰号,头部异常者,来源于中世纪英语、古英语,含义是“头”(head);[英格兰人姓氏] 黑德。地貌名称,含义是“山,溪流源头或谷顶”(hill,head of a stream or valley);

misdirection
misdirection /ˌmisdiˈrekʃən/n. 指示错误,写错;

vital
vital /ˈvaitəl/adj. 极重要的, 必不可少的;维持生命所必需的; 生命的;有生气的, 充满生机的, 生气勃勃的, 热情洋溢的;生命攸关的;关键性的,紧要的;致命的,严重的,危害生命的;n. [复数] (维持生命的)重要器官(如心、脑、肺等);[复数]  重要组成部分;要害;核心;枢纽;命脉;The analysis of what kind of temperament you possess is vital.分析一下你有什么样的气质是十分重要的。We must try to ensure that vital food supplies are maintained.我们必须确保维持生命所必需的食物之供应。His vital and cheerful manner filled the whole team with courage.他那充满生机、欢快的态度使整个队伍充满了勇气。VITALabbr. variable initialized translator for algorithmic languages 算法语言可变初始化翻译程序;Variably Initialized Translator for Algorithmic Languages 算法语言的可变初始化的翻译器;virtual information technology architecture & lifecycle 虚拟信息技术体系结构和寿命期;VMS integrated technology for affordable life cycle cost 决定汽车管理系统使用期费用的系统集成技术;

the
the /ðə/art. (指已提到的人[物]);(指说话人与听者已知的人[物]);(用于独一无二的事物前);(与形容词最高级和序数词连用);(在单数名词前表示一类人[物]);(用于江河、山脉等名称之前);(与乐器名称连用);(表示数量)每; 每一;(用于形容词前表示一类人);It's her room.The room is bright and clean.这是她的房间。这房间明亮整洁。Do you like the book?你喜欢这本书吗?The sun is like a great ball of fire.太阳像个巨大的火球。September is the ninth month of the year.九月是一年中的第九个月。The horse is a useful animal.马是有用的动物。The Pacific Ocean is the biggest ocean in the earth.太平洋是地球上最大的海洋。He is good at the piano.他擅长弹钢琴。The worker is paid by the hour.这个工人的工资按小时计算。The old are apt to catch a cold.老人容易患感冒。THEabbr. Technical Help to Exporters <英>出口商的技术协助;

worshipped
worship /ˈwə:ʃip/vt. 崇拜; 尊崇;vi. 做礼拜;热爱;爱慕,崇拜(尤指达到看不到缺点的地步);n. (对治安官或市长的尊称)阁下;A miser worships money.守财奴崇拜金钱。Don't talk while you are worshipping.你们做礼拜时别讲话。

elevation
elevation /ˌeləˈveɪʃən/n. 提升, 提高, 晋级;海拔;(建筑物的)正视图, 立体图;高地;高处;(水平或数量)提高,升高,增加;The house is at an elevation of 2, 000 metres.那幢房子位于海拔两千米的高处。

badgering
badger /ˈbædʒə/n. 獾, 穴熊;獾皮, 獾毛;<动><澳>毛鼻袋熊;袋狸;(大写)獾州人(美国威斯康星州人的别称);(大写)獾州人(美国威斯康星州人的别称);vt. 纠缠不休, 烦扰, 吵着要;The sharp sound of a twig snapping scared the badger away.细枝突然折断的刺耳声把獾惊跑了。My girlfriend badgered me to buy a necklace for her.我的女朋友纠缠着要我给她买一条项链。Badgern. [英格兰人姓氏] 巴杰。住所名称,来源于古英语人名Bacga+“岭”(ridge);[英格兰人姓氏] 巴杰。职业名称,制袋人或商贩;

Captain
captain /ˈkæptin/n. 船长, 机长;上尉, 队长, 首领;首领;领导者;(尤指运动队的)队长;(美国警察局的)副巡长;(美国消防署的)中队长;vt. 担任队长(或船长);CAPTAINabbr. character and pattern telephone access information network 图文电话接入信息网络;computer-aided processing and terminal access information network 计算机辅助处理与终端接入信息网络;

Trek
trek /trek/vi. 艰苦跋涉, 徒步旅行;n. 远距离行走;长途跋涉,艰难的旅程(尤指在山区);vt. & vi. (尤指在山中)远足,徒步旅行;游山玩水;They trekked for three days along the banks of the Zambezi.他们沿着赞比西河河岸跋涉了三天。

intellect
intellect /ˈintəlekt/n. (尤指高等的)智力,思维逻辑领悟力;才智非凡的人; 知识分子;智力高的人;才智超群的人;Newton is a man of great intellect.牛顿有非凡的才智。He was one of the most formidable intellects of his time.他是他那时代的盖世奇才。

dynamic
dynamic /daiˈnæmik/adj. 有活力的, 强有力的;不断变化的;动力的, 动态的;充满活力的;精力充沛的;发展变化的;效率高的;精悍的;有生气的;能动的;动力学的;力学的;【医学】官能的,功能的,机能的;n. (人或事物)相互作用的方式,动态;力学;动力学; 动力;力度;力度变化;活力;a dynamic young businessman 生气勃勃的年轻商人 This is a dynamic world.这是一个不断变化的世界。There is a dynamic ball in the computer.在电脑里有个动态的球。

wore
wear tov. 磨成;wore /wɔ:, wəʊr/(wear的过去式);wear /wɛə/n. 穿, 戴;衣服;磨损, 损耗;使用, 用坏;耐用性, 耐穿;穿戴的东西;服装;流行的时装;入时的打扮;调转船向下风;vt. 穿着, 戴着; 蓄, 留; 擦;呈现; 显出;磨成, 擦成; 因不断使用而造成;同意, 接受;(船)升(旗);挂(旗);使疲乏,使筋疲力尽;折磨;调转(船)向下风(tack 之对);vt. & vi. 磨损, 变旧, 用坏, 穿旧;保持某种状态;vi. (船)转向下风;This suit has been in constant wear for two years.这一套衣服已连续穿了两年。The shop sells children's wear.这家商店出售童装。Look at the wear on these shoes.看看这双鞋子磨损的样子。These shoes I bought last week are already showing signs of wear.我上周买的这双鞋已经快破了。There's a lot of wear in these tyres.这些轮胎经久耐用。He's wearing a new coat.他穿着一件新外套。He wore a smile.他面带笑容。His trousers had been worn into holes.他的裤子已经穿破了。Will your father wear this idea?你父亲会接受这个主意吗?The ship is wearing its colours.那条船挂着船旗。This cloth wears well.这种布很耐穿。The house wore a neglected look.这房子给人一种没人照料的印象。Wearn. [英格兰人姓氏] 韦尔。地貌名称,英格兰北部河流名,可能来源于凯尔特语,含义是“水”(water);[英格兰人姓氏] 韦尔。地貌名称,坝或堰;

professed
professedadj. 公开声称的,伪称的,已立誓信教的;profess /prəˈfes/vt. 声称; 宣称; 公开表明;信奉,信仰(某一宗教);妄称;伪称;声称;He professed Islam.他表白信仰伊斯兰教。

subordinates
subordinate /səˈbɔ:dinit/adj. 级别或职位较低的, 下级的;次要的, 附属的;vt. 从属;A private is subordinate to a corporal.列兵的级别低于下士。All other considerations are subordinate to our need for steady profits.比起我们需要稳定的利润来说, 其他需要考虑的事都是次要的。

chops
chops /tʃɔps/n. 摆簧夹;CHOPSabbr. Chief of Operations 主要操作;

fascinating
fascinating /ˈfæsineitiŋ/adj. 迷人的, 有极大吸引力的;The changing vivid colours of the sunset are really fascinating.日落时变化多端的色彩确实使人心醉神迷。fascinate /ˈfæsineit/vt. 使着迷, 使极感兴趣;慑住…使动弹不得;Her beauty fascinated every boy.她的美貌使所有的男孩子都着了迷。The serpent fascinated its prey.这条蛇震慑住了它要捕食的动物。

technological
technological /ˌteknəˈlɔdʒɪkəl/adj. 技术上的;工艺(学)的;由于技术原因的,因技术革新而造成的;adv. 技术上地;His parents are scientific and technological workers.他的父母都是科技工作者。a technological process工艺规程;工艺过程technological unemployment因采用新技术而造成的失业

advancements
advancement /ədˈvɑ:nsmənt/n. (工作、社会等级等的)晋升,提升,提拔;促进;推动;发展; 前进;增加;提高;垫付;His advancement to major came two years ago.他于两年前被提升为少校。advancement in career事业上进展;名扬天下;荣华富贵a slow advancement in pay工资的缓慢增长

turbolift


heroic
heroic /hiˈrəuik/adj. 有英雄气概的, 英雄的, 英勇的;Many people have heard of the man's heroic deeds.许多人都已经听说了这个人的英雄事迹。

Wrath
wrath /ræθ/n. 〈正式〉愤怒, 狂怒, 盛怒;His silence marked his wrath.他的沉默表明了他的愤怒。

Khan
khan /kɑ:n, kæn/n. 可汗,汗;n. Genghis Khan’s armies destroyed everything in their path.成吉思汗的军队所过之处都被烧杀抢掠光了。

cadets
cadet /kəˈdet/n. 陆军或海军学校学员;候补军官,候补警官;(常作名词修饰语)培训生,见习生;(常作名词修饰语)次子;幼子;弟弟;a cadet in the armed forces军队里的军校学员Cadetsabbr. Constitutional Democrats (in czarist Russia) 宪法民主主义者(俄沙皇时期);Cadetn. [人名] 卡德特;CADETabbr. computer-aided design and electrical test 计算机辅助设计与电气测试;computer-aided design of experimental transistor 计算机辅助实验晶体管设计;

stead
stead /sted/n. 代替某人;代替某人/某物;Foxton was dismissed and John Smith was appointed in his stead.福克斯顿被解职了,约翰·史密斯被任命接替他。Steadn. [英格兰人姓氏] 斯特德。住所名称,来源于古英语,含义是“庄园,农场”(estate,farm);[英格兰人姓氏] 斯特德。绰号,或职业名称,来源于中世纪英语,含义是“种马”(stud horse,stallion);

carnival
carnival /ˈkɑ:nəvəl/n. 狂欢节;嘉年华会;激动人心的事物的组合;五彩缤纷的颜色组合;I got some good shots of the carnival.我有几个狂欢节的精彩镜头。Carnivalabbr. Carnival Cruise Lines 嘉年华游轮船队(班轮公司代码);

buffed
buff /bʌf/adj. 浅黄褐色的;米色的;浅黄皮革制的;<美,俚>健美的;n. 黄褐色软皮革(尤指水牛皮或黄牛皮革);黄皮军装上衣;米色;浅黄褐色;(包着皮或布的)擦拭轮(或棒等);抛光轮;爱好者;行家里手;一丝不挂;赤裸;vt. 用软物擦亮(金属);使皮革柔软;减低(力量);减弱;vi. 作缓冲器,缓冲;She was wearing a buff uniform.她穿着一身米色制服。a railway buff火车迷I’m sure I saw him swimming in the buff!我确实看见他赤身裸体在游泳!Buff up the paintwork with a soft cloth.用块柔软的布把漆面擦亮。Buffn. [人名] 巴夫;BUFFabbr. Big Ugly Fat Fellow 大胖丑轰炸机(空军B-52八引擎轰炸机的绰号);

hip
hip /hip/n. 臀部, 屁股; 臀部…的; 野蔷薇果;臀围(尺寸);【建筑学】屋脊,斜脊;时髦,漂亮;adj. (衣服、音乐等方面)时髦的,赶时髦的;vt. 使…的髋关节脱臼,损伤…的髋部;【建筑学】给(房屋)建屋脊;使知晓,使了解,告诉;使消息灵通;使警觉;Women have rounder hips than men.女人的臀部比男人的圆。He was hipped when he dropped from the tree.他从树上跌落了下来,把髋关节摔脱了臼。It's time to hip him to the secrets.该让他了解内情了。HIPabbr. High Impact Polystyrene 耐冲击性聚苯乙烯;Hipabbr. hippocampus 海马(回);Soviet Mi-8transport helicopter 河马式直升机(代号);

midway
midway /ˈmɪdˌweɪ/adv. 在(时间的)中途;在两地之间;When he’s midway through,he ticked over.他讲到一半,就支支吾吾起来。

gvr


squin


squirt
squirt /skwɜ:t/vt. & vi. (指液体或粉末) 喷出,喷射;n. 喷射出的一股液体;妄自尊大的年轻人;不知天高地厚的人;Water squirted out.水喷出来了。

leaned
leanedlean的过去式和过去分词;lean /li:n/vt. & vi. (使)倾斜, 屈身;vt. 倚, 靠; 依赖;使斜靠; 使变瘦;使瘦弱;adj. 瘦的; 少脂肪的;瘦且健康的;贫瘠的; 收益差的;难以赚钱的;生产不出(食物等)的;贫乏的; 精干的;效率高的;简洁的;尖锐的;犀利的;直率的;n. 瘦肉;倾向;倾斜;倾斜度;收益少的事务;vi. 倾向于(某种观点、意见或态度等)(与to 或 toward连用);The postbox leans a little bit.这个邮筒有点倾斜。The teacher was leaned out by his long illness.长年生病使这位老师变得消瘦。He has a lean handsome face.他的脸清瘦而英俊。In recent years, the cinema has fallen on lean times.近几年, 电影业遇上了不景气时期。In his political opinions he leans toward the Labour Party.他的政见倾向于工党。Leann. [英格兰人姓氏] 利恩。绰号,瘦子,来源于中世纪英语,含义是“瘦的”(lean);[爱尔兰姓氏] 利恩。McLean的简称;[爱尔兰姓氏] 利恩。盖尔语姓氏的英语形式,来源于别名,含义是“矛,标枪”(spear,javelin);[爱尔兰姓氏] 利恩。盖尔语姓氏的英语形式,来源于人名,含义是“灰色的”(grey);

Tenacity
tenacity /tiˈnæsɪti:/n. 固执;坚持,顽强,不屈不挠;坚韧,韧性;(记忆等的)保持力;Tenacity is the bridge to success.坚韧是通向成功的桥。

discretionary
discretionary /dɪˈskreʃəˌneri:/adj. 任意的,无条件的;自由决定的;酌情行事的;便宜行事的;The judge has the power to make discretionary awards.法官有权自行作出裁决,决定赔偿额。

cynics
cynic /ˈsɪnɪk/n. 愤世嫉俗者,讽世者;Cynics believe that finding a good husband these days is a game of chance.愤世嫉俗者认为,现在要找到一个好丈夫是一件碰运气的事情。

cynicism
cynicism /ˈsɪnɪˌsɪzəm/n. 讥笑;讥讽的言词;愤世嫉俗;玩世不恭;犬儒主义;There was not a trace of cynicism in his voice.他的语气里没有一丝挖苦。He spoke in a tone of weary cynicism.他用一种愤世嫉俗的口气说话。

cluttering
cluttering【医】 言语急促;clutter /ˈklʌtə/n. 杂物, 零乱的东西,凌乱地塞满,乱堆放;零乱,杂乱的东西(尤指不需要的或无用的);vt. 乱糟糟地堆满;把…弄得很乱;(以…) 塞满…;We’ll have to clear up all this clutter.我们得把这一切凌乱的东西整理清楚。The cat managed to find a spot to sleep amidst all the clutter of my study.猫儿设法在我一片零乱的书房中找了个地方睡觉。I’m sick of all these books cluttering up my office.我讨厌办公室里乱糟糟地堆放着这些书。Cluttern. [人名] 克拉特;

couning
counabbr. councillor 顾问,参赞;counsel 商议,劝告;律师,辩护人;Counabbr. Council 政务会,理事会,委员会,参议会,讨论会议,顾问班子,立法班子;counsellor 顾问,参赞,律师;County 县,郡;

styrofoam
styrofoam /ˈstairəfəum/n. 泡沫塑料;聚苯乙烯;Styrofoamn. 聚苯乙烯泡沫塑料;

beads
beads玻璃粉;bead /bi:d/n. (空心)小珠子;水珠, (液体的)小滴;珠子项链;She was wearing a string of green beads round her neck.她脖子上戴着一串绿色的珠子。His face was covered with beads of sweat.他满脸都是汗珠。BEAdabbr. Barrett esophagus-associated adenocarcinomas 巴列特食管相关的腺癌;BEADabbr. beginning extended area descriptor 起始扩充区描述符;

quest
quest /kwest/n. 探求, 寻找;vt. 寻找; 探索;Man will suffer many disappointments in his quest for truth.人类在探索真理过程中必然会遭受挫折。QuESTabbr. quad Ethernet switching transceiver 四通道以太网交换收发器;QUESTabbr. quadrupole effect for stepper technology 步进机四极效应技术;Quality Electrical Systems Test 电气系统的质量测试;quality of upper extremity skills test 上肢技巧质量测试;quality, utilization, effectiveness, statistically tabulated 质量,利用,效率,统计表;queen urology examination skills training 奎恩泌尿学检查技巧训练;Queens Educational and Social Team 女王教育和社交组;quick environmental scanning technique 快速环境扫描技术;

parroting
parrot /ˈpærət/n. 鹦鹉;应声虫, 学舌者;vt. 机械地重复;鹦鹉学舌;It is not a writer's job to play the parrot.作家绝不可鹦鹉学舌。Parrotn. [英格兰人姓氏] 帕罗特。Parrott的变体;

oddball
oddball /ˈɔdbɔ:l/adj. 古怪的;n. 古怪的人;

villain
villain /ˈvilən/n. 恶棍; 歹徒; 坏人;流氓;罪犯;淘气鬼; 坏蛋;(小说、戏剧等中的)反面人物, 反派角色; 坏人;He was financially involved with a villain.他在经济上与一个恶棍混在了一起。He was cast as the villain.他饰演那个反面人物。Villainn. [人名] 维伦;

proof
proof /pru:f/n. 证明, 论证; 证据, 证物;校样, 样张;检验;证实;证明;求证;验算;(酒的)标准酒精度;adj. 防…的;抗…的;能抵御;能防范;可防护;vt. 给(织物)做防护处理;使防水(或防火等);印…的校样;Is the claim capable of proof?这要求能证明是合理的吗?Miss Ada has just sent me the proofs of her new book.埃达小姐刚把她新书的校样送给我。PROOFabbr. Parole Resource Office and Orientation Facility 假释资格审查办公室及认定机构(新泽西泽西城);

geeky
geekyadj. 〈俚〉令人讨厌的;

confession
confession /kənˈfeʃən/n. (对使自己羞愧或尴尬的事的)表白,承认;自首, 供认;声明, 表白(指宗教信仰);(向神父的)忏悔, 告解;I’ve got a confession to make, I scraped your car when I was parking mine.有件事我得向你讲出来, 我在停放汽车时把你的车子刮坏了。

Imagineer
imagine /iˈmædʒin/vt. 想像, 设想;料想, 猜想;想;误认为,胡乱猜测;I can imagine the scene clearly in my mind.我可以清楚地想像出那个情景。There's nobody following us—you're just imagining it!没有人跟着我们——你只不过是猜想而已。He is always imagining dangers that don't exist.他总是想着那些其实并不存在的危险。

hepatitis
hepatitis /ˌhepəˈtaɪtɪs/n. 肝炎;She was tested for hepatitis.她接受过肝炎检查。

jaundice
jaundice /ˈdʒɔ:ndɪs, ˈdʒɑ:n-/n. 黄疸病;偏见;jaundice in premature infants早产婴儿的黃疸病

wishful
wishful /ˈwɪʃfəl/adj. 怀有希望的,表达愿望的;单凭主观愿望的想法;一廂情愿;adv. 怀有希望地;Such wishful thinking of theirs will never be realized.他们的那种痴心妄想永远也不会实现。

mortality
mortality /mɔ:ˈtælɪti:/n. 必死性;大量死亡;死亡率;We aren’t gods: we must accept our mortality.我们不是神:要死就得死。Infant mortality is a highly sensitive barometer of socio-economic conditions.婴儿死亡率能够充分反映社会经济状况。

hypothesizing
hypothesize /haiˈpɔθəsaiz/v. 假设,假定,猜测;

Ld
LDabbr. Laser Disc 激光视盘;Ldabbr. Leopold 利奥波德;Limited 有限的,狭窄的,缺乏创见的,高级快车;lord 勋爵;老爷;

scure
scure【经】 保证; 安全的;

put
put off延期,推迟;拖延;阻碍做某事;(停车)让某人下;使分心;关掉;敷衍, 推诿;脱去(衣、帽等);丢弃, 摆脱;They decided to put the meeting off until after Christmas.他们决定把会议推迟到圣诞节以后。I wanted to say something, but her face quite put me off.我本来要说几句, 但看到她的脸色, 又没有勇气开口了。Ask the conductor to put you off at the Odeon.告诉售票员在奥汀提醒你下车。I don't like music playing when I'm working. It puts me off.我不喜欢工作时放音乐, 那会使我分心。Please put off all the lights as you leave the building.离开这所房子时, 请你把所有的灯都关上。When he asked her to name a day for their wedding, she put him off.当他要她订个结婚的日子时, 她却支支吾吾不说。Please put off your shoes before entering this holy building.在进入这所神圣的殿堂之前, 请把鞋脱掉。You must put off your doubts.你必须消除你的疑虑。put /put/vt. 放; 置;使处于(某种状态);表达, 叙述, 说明;给予(重视、信任、价值等);给予(重视、信任、价值等);vt. & vi.  使感觉到;使受到…的影响; 使感觉到;使受到…的影响;vi. 猛推,用力插入;将…送往,使…前往;使与…连接,安装;(在…上)书写,记,做标记;使处于(某状态或情况);把…视为(或列为);说,表达;推;n. [方]笨蛋; 怪人;对策;The boy forgot where he put his textbook.那男孩忘记把课本放在什么地方了。It's a wonderful scheme, and he's just the man to put it into effect.这是一个很好的计划, 而他正是实施这个计划的人选。The councillors put the problem of downtown parking before the mayor.议员们向市长提出了市内停车的问题。Bernanke Put伯南克对策PUTabbr. physical unit table 物理部件表;product under test 被测产品;program update tape 程序更改带;programmable unijunction transistor 可编程单结晶体管;putamen 壳核;被壳状部;壳(豆状核);Putabbr. proline utilization 脯氨酸利用;

advocates
advocate /ˈædvəkeit/vt. 提倡, 主张;拥护;鼓吹;为…辩护;n. 提倡者, 拥护者;辩护律师, 辩护人;(辩护)律师,专门律师,出庭律师(作为头衔用于保留古罗马法律实质的国家和地区,如苏格兰;亦用于英国海事法庭等);[A-]基督;I don't advocate doing such things.我不主张干这样的事情。He is an advocate of more airplanes and fewer warships.他是一个提倡多造飞机、少造军舰的人。He got the best advocate in town to defend him.他请城里最好的律师为他辩护。

brochure
brochure /ˈbrəuʃuə/n. 小册子;(某地、某旅馆等的)情况介绍手册,小册子,说明书;(印成小册子的)论文;They brought home heaps of travel brochures.他们将成堆的旅行手册带回家。

conjured
conjure up用魔法召(鬼); 凭幻想(或用魔法)做出;The woman practising witchcraft claimed that she could conjure up the spirits of the dead.那个女巫说她能用魔法召唤亡灵。conjure /ˈkɔndʒə, kənˈdʒʊə/vt. 用魔术变出;祈求, 恳求;vi. 变戏法, 变魔术;使魔术般地消失;(变魔术般地) 使…出现;使…呈现于脑际;使想起;念咒招魂;The magician conjured a rabbit out of his hat.魔术师从他的帽子里变出一只兔子。He conjured them with his dying breath to look after his children.他临终时恳求他们照顾他的孩子。Paul’s very good at conjuring.保罗很会变戏法。His very funny joke soon conjured my anger away.他讲了个十分有趣的笑话,使得我的怒气顿消。She conjured up a three-course meal in half an hour!她用半小时变出了一顿有三道菜的饭!The word ‘birthday’ conjures up images of presents and parties.“生日”这个词使人想起礼物和聚会的情景。

oxic


toxic
toxic /ˈtɔksik/adj. 有毒的;因中毒引起的;When spilled into the sea, oil can be toxic to marine plants and animals.石油溢入海洋可能危害海洋生物。

regimen
regimen /ˈredʒəmən, -ˌmen/n. (为病人规定的)生活规则,养生法;养生之道;We used a combined regimen of injection treatment and radiation therapy.我们采用了针剂注射和放射治疗相结合的方法。

intestiiree


intestine
intestine /ɪnˈtestɪn/n. 肠;The tapeworm is an inhabitant of the intestine.绦虫是栖居肠内的寄生虫。

abdomen
abdomen /ˈæbdəmən, æbˈdəʊmən/n. 腹(部);adj. 腹部的;adv. 以腹部地;The nurse tapped the patient’s abdomen.护士给病人放出腹水。Abdomen<拉>腹;

oncologist
oncologist/ɒŋˈkɒlədʒıst/n.肿瘤学家

qualmsl


qualms
qualmsn. 不安;良心之谴责;qualm /kwɑ:m, kwɔ:m/n. (对自己行为的)顾虑,不安 (~ about sth);He had been working very hard so he had no qualms about taking a few days off.他一直辛勤工作,所以休息几天他觉得心安理得。

ietastasis


metastasis
metastasis /məˈtæstəsis/n. 转移;

metastasized
metastasize /məˈtæstəˌsaiz/vi. 转移;

rationally
rationallyadv. 讲道理地,理性地;

preemptive
preemptive /pri:ˈemptɪv/n. 先买的;有先买权的;先发制人的;preemptive authority.先买权

grim
grim /ɡrim/adj. 严酷的, 无情的;讨厌的, 糟糕的;严厉的;阴冷的,阴森凄凉的;有病的,不舒服的;His expression was grim when he told them they had lost their jobs.当他告诉他们说他们已被解雇时, 他的表情十分冷酷。I've had a grim day.我过了不愉快的一天。Grimn. [英格兰人姓氏] 格里姆。绰号,来源于古英语,含义是“严厉的”(stern,severe);

curative
curative /ˈkjuərətiv/adj. 医疗的;n. 药品;

f
f(以态度、言语、抚摸)表示爱抚;(演奏或歌唱)强,强有力;Fn. 字母F;

bereft
bereft /bɪˈreft/adj. 失去(某种能力或性质);缺少…的;失去亲人的;After the fire swallowed his cottage,the old man could not but feel utterly bereft.在一场大火吞噬了他的草屋之后,老人唯一的感觉就是他已经一无所有了。bereave /bɪˈri:v/vt. (尤指死亡)使丧失(亲人、朋友等);使孤寂,使凄凉;使失去(希望、生命等);<废>抢走(财物);Illness bereaved her of her husband.疾病夺去了她的丈夫。

